discounttirecenters.com 2015-04-07

# DTC Privacy Policy for Discount tires and wheels, truck, 4x4 and suv tires, car rims, car wheels, aftermarket wheels, custom wheels

Your privacy is very important to Discount Tire Centers, and we are committed to protecting it. You are welcome to explore our web site without providing any information about yourself. When you visit and navigate our Web site, we will not collect personal information about you unless you provide us that information voluntarily. By "personal information," we mean data that is unique to an individual, such as a name, address, e-mail address or telephone number. 

What information does Discount Tire Centers collect from me? Our web server automatically recognizes your domain name. Our web server does not recognize your e-mail address. Most of Discount Tire Centers web site has been designed to not require the use of any personal identifiers (such as name, address, telephone number or e-mail address). IF YOU SEND US AN E-MAIL OR SUBSCRIBE TO A NEWSLETTTER, WE WILL HAVE YOUR E-MAIL ADDRESS AT OUR SITE. 

Discount Tire Centers collects and uses certain information on its web site. This information includes your IP address, information about your browser (i.e., whether you are using Netscape, Internet Explorer, etc.), and information about your Internet Service Provider (i.e., AOL, Verizon). An IP address (Internet Protocol Address) is a unique number that is used to represent every single computer in a network. All computers on the Internet have a unique IP address. None of the foregoing information will be used by Discount Tire Centers in any way, or in connection with any other information, to identify you personally. 

Discount Tire Centers uses the statistical information gathered about you and all of its users for internal statistical purposes only, e.g., to track where users go on the web site. This information is not linked to specifically identifiable individuals. This type of information will be used to aid Discount Tire Centers in adding information to its web site that will be useful for site users and that will improve the performance of our web site.

## E-Mails

When you sign up for free e-mails, we maintain information about your selections only for the purpose of sending you the e-mails. We do not use identifying personal information for any other purpose although it may be included in anonymous, aggregated statistical information. If you communicate with us by email you should understand that email is not secure against interception. If your communication includes sensitive or confidential information, please contact us by phone or mail.

Instructions for unsubscribing from e-mails are located at the bottom of each e-mail. Click the link given and request to be removed from our list.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of information that is stored on your computer's hard drive, not on our site.

As you browse DiscountTireCenters.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with DiscountTireCenters.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number.

## Disclosure of Your Information

All of the information you choose to provide us is absolutely confidential and voluntary. We will never give, sell, rent or reveal your name or address (including e-mail) to any outside party without your express consent. Discount Tire Centers will not disclose your personally identifiable information to independent third parties other than those who help us operate our site, (such as an independent third party who might help us deliver our newsletters).

When you sign up for these member services we will share your name, contact information or other information necessary for the third party to provide the services. These independent third parties will only use your information to provide the designated service, and will handle your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

## Security measures

Discount Tire Centers takes reasonable precautions to protect your personally identifiable information. When users submit personally identifiable information, it is protected both on-line and off-line.

## Notification of Changes

We will prominently post any significant changes we make to our Privacy Policy. Discount Tire Centers will use the information collected from you in accordance with the privacy policy in effect when the information was collected.

## Links to Other Web Sites

This site contains links to other sites. Discount Tire Centers is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

## Correcting and updating information

If, at any time, a correction needs to be made to existing personal information that you have voluntarily provided to the web site, users may email the webmaster at webmaster@discounttirecenters.com and request that the information be changed or deleted.

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [webmaster@discounttirecenters.com](mailto:webmaster@discounttirecenters.com).

## Copyright Information

All content at Discount Tire Centers, including graphics, logos, icons, text, and images, is the property of Discount Tire Centers and is protected by U.S. and international copyright laws.
